EDUARD PREDESCU

eduard.florin.predescu@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardpredescu/ • https://github.com/epr3

SUMMARY

I have seven years of experience working with front end technologies including but not limited to: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue.js (2+3), React + any state management, Nuxt/Next.js, Tailwind/UnoCSS). I am proficient in React and Vue for front end, Go/Node.js for back end if it is required. I have some experience with mobile apps using React Native.

EDUCATION

M.S., Economic Informatics

Graduated June 2019

Bucharest University of Economic Studies, Bucharest, RO

10

Bachelor's degree, Economic Cybernetics

Graduated June 2017

Bucharest University of Economic Studies, Bucharest, RO

10

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front End: Vue 2/3, React, Nuxt 2/3, Next.js, Remix, Tailwind, UnoCSS, Typescript, Astro, HTML5, CSS3

Back End: Go, Node.js, Fiber, Postgres, MySQL/MariaDB, Storyblok, Prismic

DevOps: AWS, Gitlab CI, Netlify, Docker

OPEN SOURCE

Radix Vue, https://radix-vue.com/: Collaborator

- Architect and implement headless components for manipulating dates and times (DatePicker, Calendar, Date-Field)
- · Architect and implement an Editable type component
- · Minor bugfixes

EXPERIENCE

FlowX.AI, Bucharest, RO (Hybrid): Senior Frontend Engineer

July 2024 - present

Cognizant Softvision, Bucharest, RO (Hybrid): Senior Software Engineer

June 2023 - July 2024

- Maintain and develop microsites/event pages for client marketing website
- Optimize and tweak Nuxt and Netlify for faster build times for client marketing website
- Handled ETL operations for migration from Prismic CMS to Storyblok CMS for client marketing website
- Refactor UI to atomic design for marketing website
- Handle serverless functions in Netlify for client marketing website
- Maintain Postgres DB for CSR App
- Develop, refactor, architect backend API in Golang (w/ Echo, later w/ Fiber) for CSR App.
- Manage docs and OpenAPI 3 definitions for CSR App
- Implement testing for CSR App
- Handle basic DevOps in Gitlab CI and AWS for CSR App

Cognizant Softvision, Bucharest, RO (Hybrid): Software Engineer

June 2020 - June 2023

Team Extension, Bucharest, RO: Front End Developer

Oct 2017 - Jun 2020

- Conducted technical interviews for front end recruitment
- Maintaining and expanding a 3D design dashboard using Vue.js, three.js and Laravel and elaborating a daily status report for the progress
- Implementing a mobile internal app using React Native for recruitment
- Maintaining and expanding a social media aggregator app based on user generated content using Vue.js
- Creating a marketing website using Vue.js and Laravel Blade Templates for a large music company

· Helping other coworkers on front end related queries

Elsaco Solutions, Bucharest, RO: Software Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017

- Maintained the company's presentation website in Wordpress
- Created a web scraper in Node.js for seeding a database for a discount management app prototype

Eau de Web, Bucharest, RO: Front End Intern

May 2016 - Sep 2016

- · Maintained http://junio.ro front end using Bootstrap, jQuery
- Maintained and expanded a marketing website using Jekyll, Bootstrap, JavaScript
- Added features for a reporting dashboard using Bootstrap and JavaScript

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

IT Member @ SiSC - Sindicatul Studenţilor din Cibernetică

Nov 2015 - Jul 2019

Managed various public facing websites for events organised by the association.

Front End Division Lead @ SiSC - Sindicatul Studentilor din Cibernetică

Jun 2016 - May 2017

Mentored new front end members and provided support on various technical challenges.

Front End Padawan @ DevAcademy

Nov 2016 - May 2017

Graduated from course and got up-to-date with front end technologies, especially Vue.js.

AWARDS

Winning Team @ Hackaton4Health 2019

https://www.startupcafe.ro/idei-si-antreprenori/liceeni-aplicatie-medicala-concurs.htm

• Developed an AR solution for surgery guidance as part of a hackaton team.